Guide to the Mabel Dodge Luhan Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.83; (2 boxes)
  - Box 31, folder 900 (Box 110, Folder 2606)
  - Box 31, folder 901 (Box 110, Folder 2607)
  - Box 32, folder 937 (Box 110, Folder 2608)
  - Box 32, folder 939 (Box 110, Folder 2609)
  - Box 32, folder 941 (Box 110, Folder 2610)
  - Box 32, folder 942 (Box 110, Folder 2611)
  - Box 33, folder 947 (Box 110, Folder 2612)
  - Box 33, folder 948 (Box 110, Folder 2613)
  - Box 33, folder 949 (Box 110, Folder 2614)
  - Box 33, folder 961 (Box 110, Folder 2615)
  - Box 33, folder 965 (Box 110, Folder 2616)
  - Box 33, folder 968 (Box 110, Folder 2617)
  - Box 34, folder 973 (Box 110, Folder 2618)
  - Box 34, folder 993 (Box 110, Folder 2619)
  - Box 34, folder 994 (Box 110, Folder 2620)
  - Box 34, folder 1003 (Box 110, Folder 2621)
  - Box 35, folder 1014 (Box 110, Folder 2622)
  - Box 35, folder 1020 (Box 110, Folder 2623)
  - Box 35, folder 1028 (Box 110, Folder 2624)
  - Box 36, folder 1030 (Box 110, Folder 2625)
  - Box 36, folder 1032 (Box 110, Folder 2626)
  - Box 36, folder 1037 (Box 110, Folder 2627)
  - Box 36, folder 1048 (Box 110, Folder 2628)
  - Box 36, folder 1053 (Box 110, Folder 2629)
  - Box 37, folder 1080 (Box 110, Folder 2630)
  - Box 37, folder 1081 (Box 110, Folder 2631)
  - Box 38, folder 1087 (Box 110, Folder 2632)
  - Box 38, folder 1097 (Box 110, Folder 2633)
  - Box 38, folder 1113 (Box 110, Folder 2634)
  - Box 38, folder 1115 (Box 110, Folder 2635)
  - Box 38, folder 1116 (Box 110, Folder 2636)
  - Box 38, folder 1117 (Box 110, Folder 2637)
  - Box 38, folder 1118 (Box 110, Folder 2638)
  - Box 38, folder 1120 (Box 110, Folder 2639)
  - Box 39, folder 1126 (Box 110, Folder 2640)
  - Box 39, folder 1127 (Box 110, Folder 2641)
  - Box 39, folder 1132 (Box 110, Folder 2642)
  - Box 39, folder 1143 (Box 110, Folder 2643)
  - Box 39, folder 1145 (Box 110, Folder 2644)
  - Box 40, folder 1163 (Box 110, Folder 2645)
  - Box 40, folder 1169 (Box 110, Folder 2646)
  - Box 40, folder 1175 (Box 110, Folder 2647)
  - Box 40, folder 1181 (Box 110, Folder 2648)
  - Box 41, folder 1234 (Box 110, Folder 2649)
  - Box 62, folder 1604 (Box 110, Folder 2650)
  - Box 62, folder 1605 (Box 110, Folder 2651)
  - Box 63, folder 1664 (Box 110, Folder 2652)
  - Box 63, folder 1718 (Box 110, Folder 2653)
  - Box 67, folder 1813 (Box 110, Folder 2653a)
  - Box 100, folder 2291 (Box 110, Folder 2654)
  - Box 100, folder 2292 (Box 110, Folder 2655)
- Restricted Fragile Oversize, 3.34; (2 boxes)
  - Box 21, folder 587 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2656)
  - Box 23, folder 647 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2657)
  - Box 29, folder 847 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2658)
  - Box 43, folder 1309 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2659)
  - Box 43, folder 1329 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2660)
  - Box 43, folder 1332 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2661)
  - Box 44, folder 1356 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2662)
  - Box 44, folder 1369 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2663)
  - Box 45, folders 1380-1383 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2664)
  - Box 46, folder 1385 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2665)
  - Box 46, folders 1388-1389 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2666)
  - Box 49, folders 1399-1400 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2667)
  - Box 55, folder 1417 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2668)
  - Box 60, folder 1511 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2669)
  - Box 61, folder 1551 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2670)
  - Box 61, folder 1560 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2671)
  - Box 61, folder 1563 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2672)
  - Box 63, folder 1694 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2673)
  - Box 63, folder 1714 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2674)
  - Box 63, folder 1722 (Box 111 (Oversize), Folder 2675)
  - Box 99, folder 2281 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2676)
  - Box 99, folder 2282 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2677)
  - Box 99, folder 2283 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2678)
  - Box 99, folder 2284 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2679)
  - Box 99, folder 2284a (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2680)
  - Box 99, folder 2285 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2681)
  - Box 102, folder 2368 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2682)
  - Box 102, folder 2369 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2683)
  - Box 102, folder 2373 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2684)
  - Box 102, folder 2374 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2685)
  - Box 102, folder 2384 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2686)
  - Box 102, folder 2390 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2687)
  - Box 102, folder 2391 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2688)
  - Box 102, folder 2393 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2689)
  - Box 102, folder 2401 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2690)
  - Box 102, folder 2402 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2691)
  - Box 102, folder 2403 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2692)
  - Box 102, folder 2406 (Box 112 (Oversize), Folder 2693)